

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Core-PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Angular, REST API, Codeligniter



Current Designation: Software Developer -PHP Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: i2i TeleSolutions

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project

Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Core-PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Angular, REST API, Codel gniter, Laravel, Git, React Js

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

I have experience as a Web Developer in backend and frontend. Hands on in application development using various web technologies. Considerable experience in the design and development of web application. Ability to learn and develop using new technology quickly.

Work Experience

i2i TeleSolutions as Software Developer -PHP

Oct 2018 to Till Date

Implement changes in current products frontend and backend technologies.

Add a new features with responsive design layouts.

Resolving Bugs

Maintainance current website, fixing library problem and resolving server related issues.

Uriah Solution as PHP Developer

Dec 2017 to Jun 2018

Skills used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Core-PHP, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, REST APIs, MySQL, Google Business API, Payment gateway, Codeigniter(beginner), Firebase, Mail Integration, TinyMCE editor, Google Map, OTP phone authentication(SMS login), Angularis 2.

Projects URL- https://www.webliststore.org/iasshiksha/, Dental CRM

Designing, writing modules code, complete testing of web-application before production(hosting), prepare for changes according to the client requirements(layout and business code) and websites maintenance(update all the scripting files and software).

Writing and debugging new REST APIs for mobile applications of the same web-application.

Maintenance of server and secure with malware, virus attacks to web-application.

Syrow as PHP Developer Oct 2017 to Nov 2017

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=4906e28ffc37b089db9d27f7d23e44b2515e5b534c130c190619150e5b...

Maintenance the company product(web-application), update all the scripting files, layout and add new features- chat box, instamojo.

URL- https://www.syrow.com/pricing-ind/

Infocampus Logics as Web Developer

Dec 2015 to Jul 2017

Skills used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Core-PHP, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, REST APIs, MySQL, Payment gateway, Codeigniter(beginner), Firebase, Mail Integration, TinyMCE editor, Google Map, Angularjs 1 and 2, Open Source tools, Nodejs

Project URL- http://www.ansuiinterior.com, http://gyanguide.com, http://www.firstenquiry.com, http://radonpackers.com, Lead generation and PIF form of the interviewer

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from Kumaun University in 2012

PG: MCA (Computers) from Visveswaraiah Technological University (VTU) in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
HTML, CSS			
BOOTSTRAP			
CORE-PHP			
JavaScript, JQuery			
Ajax, Angular			
REST APIs, Codelgniter			
Laravel			
Git, ReactJs			
MySQL, FireBase			
Mongodb			
WINDOWS			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time